{
    "subject": "Nazli_Sabri",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Fuad_I_of_Egypt",
    "human_readable": "Nazli Sabri is married to Fuad I of Egypt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8812586665153503,
            "question": "Who was Nazli Sabri married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8133714199066162,
            "question": "What is the full name of the person Nazli Sabri was married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7769970893859863,
            "question": "What is known about the relationship between Nazli Sabri and Fuad I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48375335335731506,
            "question": "Was Nazli Sabri involved in Egyptian politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2731287181377411,
            "question": "To which country did Fuad I rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2267945259809494,
            "question": "How is Nazli Sabri remembered in history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11830705404281616,
            "question": "Were there any historical events associated with their marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03144451975822449,
            "question": "Is there any information available about their family life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03049078769981861,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the era in which they lived?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.021385518833994865,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges they might have faced during their time together?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nazli Sabri is married to Fuad I of Egypt.",
            "html": "yago_25341_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the era in which they lived?",
            "html": "yago_25341_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about their family life?",
            "html": "yago_25341_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any historical events associated with their marriage?",
            "html": "yago_25341_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25341_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Nazli Sabri was married to Fuad I of Egypt. The relevant text can be found in the file paths `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25341/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt`, `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25341/re-ranker-msmarco/31.txt`, and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_25341/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Nazli Sabri and Fuad I of Egypt, including the date they were engaged, the day they got married, and that their marriage lasted for 16 years until Fuad I's death. This supports the statement that Nazli Sabri is married to Fuad I of Egypt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}